Ronen Lapushner

Cellphone: +972-50-2669606 Email: ronenk17@gmail.com Portfolio: ronen25.github.io

I am a highly motivated C/C++ developer, with more than 6 years of vast, proven experience with many environments, looking for exciting opportunities to to use my wide skill set to contribute and thrive.

Professional Skills

Languages/Platforms

- C (C99/11)
- C++ (03, 14+)
- Python 3
- Java
- QML (Qt 5+)
- Rust
- Linux/Unix, Windows

Backend

- Cross-platform development with native tools
- Multithreding
- Multiprocessing
- POSIX API
- Win32 API

GUI Frameworks

- Qt 5+
- Swing
- wxWidgets (3.x)
- Tk
- PyQt / qt-python
- dear ImGui

Software

- GCC Toolchains
- Valgrind
- LLVM Utilities
- Doxygen
- QMake/CMake/ Autotools

Experience

Cyren Software Engineer / Tech Lead

September 2016 – January 2019

- Development and maintenance of a cross-platform (Windows, *nix, MacOS), cross-architecture, full-stack application.
- Using LLVM's sanitizers to standardize and improve code quality.
- AGILE development and tight integration of customer relations.
- Granular per-architecture optimization and/or development of the product.
- Rewriting old code with C++14-compliant code.
- Reverse engineering and Documentation of previously undocumented systems.

Israeli Air Force (IAF) – Ofek Unit Programmer

December 2013 – August 2016

- Honorable discharge with very high commendations.
- Development of highly-classified logistic and automation systems.
- Conceptualization, design and implementation of advanced communications and data systems.
- Full Stack End-to-End and prototyping using different development platforms.

Education

Open University of Israel

July 2018 - Present

• B.Sc. in Computer Science, 84 average. Projected graduation: October 2022.

BASMACH Shalishut Base, Ramat-Gan, Israel

September – December 2013

• NTMM (*Nat-Mam*) Course for DevOps engineers, graduated with excellence.

Tchernichovski High School Netanya, Israel

September 2007 – June 2013

• Complete Matriculation diploma with 5 units in Computer Science and Physics.

Spoken Languages

Hebrew: Native language **English:** Native level

Recommendations will be forwarded upon request.